Mikhailov Anton

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Creations Beyond Imaginations!

Hope you are doing well and safe from Covid-19.

I have a love of Web Development and IT in general that I bring to all my work.

I am meticulous and am always learning more about my field to both stay current and to expand on my skills.

I have rich experience in Front-end Development.

I have a real love of IT and Web Development.

I find the whole field endlessly fascinating.

I am familiar with building clean, efficient, well-documented, well-structured, high-quality code projects. Also, I am very well-versed in the agile approach in project development and really love to add my creativity to the overall project implementation.

Using best practices, I provide clean, validated, pixel-perfect, responsive, and top-quality code.

Have a big experience working on websites with creative and complex layouts.

The quality of performed work is in the first place for me.

I love challenges, so feel free to reach out to me for any project and leave the rest to me.

Thank you for viewing my profile, hope we can work on a project together soon.

Employment History

Web Developer, GLOBUS LTD, Moscow, Russia

APRIL 2013 — NOVEMBER 2015

Front-end Developer, ASTRIO AGENCY, Moscow, Russia

FEBRUARY 2016 - MARCH 2019

Front-end developer, NOVA OCEAN, Moscow, Russia

AUGUST 2019 - AUGUST 2021

Education

Moscow State University

 ${\tt MARCH~2008-NOVEMBER~2012}$

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and Technology.

Details

Russia, Moscow

Skills

JavaScript: ES6,ES7,ES8

Web3.js

React.js

Redux

Next.js

HTML5

CSS3/SASS/BootStrap

Node

Blockchain Development

solidity

MySQL

Frontend Development

solidity

Web3.js

Smart contract

PHP

Languages

Russian

English

Hobbies

Skiing, Football, Tennis